What the heck is this supposed to be?
You think you're funny putting black ink
all over my spaghetti, is that right?
No, no, no, sir, not at all.
This is called a narrow de sapia.
It is a classic pasta dish made with
fresh squid ink, hence the color.
Really?
It's quite delicious. Hmm.
Say, this is delicious!
This hotel used to be a place
of class and refinement.
Now they let just anyone in here.
Signorina, accept this,
a token of your beauty.
It's beautiful!
Not as much as you.
When you remove this at night,
please think of me, and we shall
be together in your dreams.
Come on!
Did that mozzarella cheese wall
just say what I think he said?
I shall cast an enchantment upon
it, just a little love spell?
and then you will have no choice
but to fall to my passion.
You've got to be kidding!
This guy is making me sick!
And I shall spread my chum's magic
to those delicious lips of yours.
That's just ridiculous!
How could any modern woman
fall for such an obvious act?
Disgusting!
I have an idea.
Harmon de sepia.
This should stick to that little
Casanova's enchanting face for a bit.
How did he just do that?
That, that was Hamon.
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Pardon the intrusion, but there
is a phone call from a Mr.
Speedwagon, Mr. Caesar Zeppeli.
Mamma mia, I will be right
there. What? What the?
That spaghetti-brained womanizer is the
Caesar Zeppeli we came
all the way here to find?
I don't know.
Thank you.
This is the Speed Wagon Foundation.
This complex was built 28 years ago with
funds from the Ample Speed Wagon fortune.
Here all manners of science, medicine,
archaeology and more are
generously funded and
exhaustively researched for
the benefit of all humankind.
But the foundation?
also houses a darker purpose.
One to unlock the secret
of the stone masks.
The UV lights are very powerful.
Please, if you don't mind.
Introduce the snake.
It was absorbed into the stone.
Son Viento still isn't dead.
His body is defending itself somehow.
What if he finds some
way to awaken in there?
This can't be.
We must find a way to destroy him.
The monster fleets on masked vampires.
He's immortal for all we know.
What are we supposed to do?
Don't worry, Mr.
Speedwagon.
He can't do anything.
As long as he's under those UV lights,
he will remain petrified and
can pose no threat to us.
That's right.
I suppose that's a relief.
There is still more research to be
done if we are to understand him fully.
See those?
Those pictures were taken in the cave
where we originally found San Viento.
Inspect them carefully.
The horns!
They all have different types of horns!
So if the one on the bottom
is supposed to be San Viento?
then who are the others?
According to von Stroheim,
the Germans have uncovered another
pillar at an undisclosed location?
somewhere on the European continent.
Is that true?
Their faces are stacked
vertically in this picture.
Speaking historically,
I would theorize that this indicates
status or rank among the three Pillar Men.
Jojo and I are headed to Rome.
Von Stroheim told him
that we must go there
in order to find the
person who can help us.
And it turns out that person is none
other than the grandson of Will A.
Zeppeli, Caesar Zeppeli!
Tell me, where might you be from?
Would you like me to take a picture?
Perhaps one of you in the fountain?
Huh?
Boy, the birds in this
country sure are friendly.
They seem much smarter than the
men here, too, don't you think?
Knock it off, Jojo.
We didn't come all this way for nothing.
The two of you better start talking.
Mr.
Speedwagon, I'm sorry, but not a chance.
My grandfather died
tragically 50 years ago.
My father then took up his torch
and spent his life hunting the mask.
We Italians have the strongest familial
bonds of any culture in the world.
We are very proud of that tradition.
It is everything to us.
That's something he'll never understand.
In fact, you told me he didn't know about
his own grandfather until just recently.
A true man knows his history.
Tell me this true man is
your host family this dumb.
That's not fair, Caesar.
Jojo didn't know anything because
I kept it all a secret from him.
I don't think that's any excuse.
I heard about Straizo,
and I was impressed to find out that
he fought one of the Pillar Men.
But I wanted to see for myself how
tough he was, so I waited at the hotel.
And I'm disappointed to say that his
Hamon skills leave much to be desired.
His Hamon is weak.
It's worthless.
His defeat of the Pillar Man
was nothing but blind luck!
I won't be forced to
work with this imbecile!
Caesar, just relax for a moment.
Jojo is still trading...
We're done with the niceties here.
I'm going to have to settle
this with a good thrashing.
Hamon as weak as yours couldn't pluck
the petals off this delicate flower.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you couldn't even
beat one of those pigeons!
Are you gonna fight me or not?
If there's any mocking to be
done here, I'll take care of it!
Thank you kindly!
You bastard!
You gave this woman a Hamon kiss!
Like I just said, your weak Hamon
couldn't even defeat a woman. Sad.
I must not intervene here.
This will be a good lesson for Jojo.
Overcoming this will
only make him stronger.
Huh.
What did I tell you?
My grandfather might still be alive if
your grandfather hadn't gotten his way.
I refuse to accept your kind.
Your pathetic blood. That's enough.
You've crossed the line now.
Stop.
I've got this.
Someone as arrogant as you just couldn't
resist insulting my entire family,
could you?
Like to see my maneuver sure
to eliminate the Pillar Men?
It's a clean technique.
Behold, my Hamon Baby Lanchot.
It's important to keep oneself clean.
I, myself, have a thin layer of
soap on my clothes at all times!
You're looking a little
dirty yourself, there!
Joestar!
Well, I am impressed that
you're still conscious,
but your weak little Hamon
couldn't even pop a bubble.
Just look at you.
Your breath is already all over
the place enjoy your stage you
start and next you'll say now I'll
lift my harm on spell signorina.
Thank you
And now I'll lift my
hum on spell signorina.
Thank you
While that woman was throttling me,
I filled a pigeon with as much hamon as
I could and hid it away in her mouth.
I knew you'd kiss her,
either because you had to withdraw
your hamon or just to show off.
So I was right.
Turns out that you couldn't
even beat a pigeon.
Ah, what a day.
Honestly, just who does
this jerk think he is?
Grant's standing like that
just to sit down in a chair.
I really can't stand people like him.
If only I had a technique
like his bubble launcher.
I'd be able to teach
him some humility then.
I have to get stronger with my hamon.
But training is always such a hassle.
Let's see how our little friend
handles a game of chance.
I saw that Jojo deal the cards right.
Only cowards cheat.
Whatever, do you?
Deal the cards properly, Joestar.
Or play elsewhere.
Fancy that.
Well, that didn't work.
Pathetic.
You should be ashamed that you have to
resort to cheating and gimmicks to beat me.
You really are serious about cleanliness.
This mirror is spotless.
Stop provoking me, Joe Star!
Oh, I haven't even started! Calm down!
It's been eight hours, Caesar.
Do you mind telling us
what we're waiting for?
What are we waiting for?
Here's your answer.
What the hell is a German
soldier doing here?
It looks like we're clear.
Just who do you think
guards the Pillowman?
He'll get us in there.
Behave yourself.
Again with the Germans?
Stop the Pillar Men before they awake.
How's the beauty?
Now don't be embarrassed you
have a girlfriend back home.
Well, she's...
Actually, the truth is...
I'll be going home next week so we
can finally get married. Really?
Mamma mia!
Congratulations, Mark!
I was his wingman when he
picked her up, you know.
He was so nervous.
Heartwarming.
Please don't get us all killed here.
And please stop cuddling with
the wheel if you don't mind.
I wanted to ask you, Jojo, do
you have a girlfriend back home?
I'll take that as a no, but
you're such a great catch.
Why doesn't anyone want to date you?
Perhaps they're all too
busy washing their hair, eh?
Where does this pompous ass get
off talking to me like that?
Once I develop my own killer technique,
I'll show him a thing or two, or three.
Look, there's something on his head!
I don't think that was there before!
Calm down.
They're just rocks as long as
they're under those UV lights.
No need to worry.
Now get a closer look! Yes, sir!
The death of Von Strauheim's team
is an important lesson to us all.
Once we cut this pillar out,
we'll have to seal it so that it will
never see the light of day again.
I can't tell what that dark spot is.
It looks like a hole, but
it might just be a shadow.
Get a closer look.
Do you hear that?
His horn!
He's supposed to be petrified!
He's making up!
Quickly, bring out more UV
lamps! Yes, sir! Schnell!
This can't be happening!
He's blocking out the lights
with the blood of my own man!
I see the world has undergone
significant changes during my slumber.
These insignificant inventions
must be quite popular here.
What did he say?
I said your pitiful illuminations
are no match against my power!
My hands!
We're stuck together!
Mama, now is the time.
Awaken, my masters!
Somehow this doesn't surprise me.
The famous mouth of truth was a
secret entrance all this time.
You can really feel the
chill of the dead here.
Caesar, what sort of effects has your
Hormone had on the sleeping pillar?
Men hormone is only useful on the living.
No reason to waste.
as my power's on stone.
We can't learn anything
if they're not alive.
I'm surprised you Germans don't have
more than zero guards down here.
It's a little quiet. Hello!
Stop being foolish, Jojo.
Wait, something's wrong.
He's right, there should be guards
posted all around this place.
Really?
Why didn't anyone tell me
there were bats in here?
Gross, I stepped in bat tongue!
And I just cleaned these.
Wait, those are...
They're husks of dead soldiers.
What the hell happened to them?
They're all dead!
Stop where you are!
Whoever did this could still be here!
We don't know what's out there!
What is that?
I can't believe it!
They're alive!
Run the way, Mark!
Mark!
Get out of there now!
No!
Mark!
Mark, no!
Ceaser! Ceaser!
What have they done?
They just walked right through your
friend like he wasn't even there!
The Pillar Men have
awoken with such massive
power that we barely even exist to them!
We may as well be nothing more than
a colony of ants beneath their feet!
It appears to be night outside, Wamu.
That is correct, Lord Kars.
And what shall be your bidding?
Easy.
We will be searching for the
whereabouts of the Red Stone of Asia.
The stone is the last piece we
need in order to complete the mask.
Then, we will unleash its power.
Of course, Master ACDC.
However, the human world has changed
much over the years that we slumbered.
Long ago, it was the Emperor of
Rome who possessed the stone.
Unfortunately, I am
certain that age has ended.
Well then, we simply need to find where
it is the stone currently calls home.
They say the Emperor cherished
the stone above all things.
I believe that the humans of
today still tell stories of it.
I shall retrieve the
stone for you, my master.
There's time, Wamuu.
For the moment, then.
Let us go outside and observe the changes
that have occurred in the human world.
Wamuu!
Explain your insolence!
Stay your hand, ACDC.
I apologize, Lord Kars.
Of course.
It had slipped my mind that
you possess a reflexive attack
against anyone who dares to walk
across the depths of your shadow.
It has been 2,000 years, after all.
I have offended you, my lord.
I will accept whatever
punishment you see fit.
I simply cannot accept your apology.
Your innate fighting spirit is
what makes you a great warrior,
and that is why I trust you.
The fault is my own for
treading upon your darkness.
Please forgive my transgression.
You are too kind.
Rise, Wamuu.
Yes, Master.
Caesar!
Kill me, please! Do it!
You've got to kill me now! I can't.
It's...
it's getting so cold. Please, Caesar.
I'm...
I'm so scared.
I couldn't feel anything
at first, but now the pain.
Please, Caesar, you've got to kill me now.
Mark, there's nothing we can do.
I can't do anything to
help this poor bastard.
I feel so powerless.
I must control myself.
I feel like I'm going to explode.
Goodbye, friend.
Caesar.
Give out my love, Caesar!
I
promise.
He was so young.
His whole life ahead of him.
He worked hard for a living.
He loved his family dearly.
He loved his girl and his country.
He was a good person.
Clean cut, the boy next door.
And they killed him.
Now they die!
Caesar!
Don't you dare get in my way, Jojo!
I'm going to enjoy every second of this!
This is personal!
I'll destroy these things myself!
We're spitting for the man.
We're closer to all the land.
We're probably no more.
But in frames of sand.
He's got to lose all the time.
I want to face his mind in my head.
Next to your deeper fears.
He stands around the five million years.
I'll give you round the night.
Now I'm sick and tired
of all this talking.
Explain yourself.
What are you trying to get at?
I knew he was spineless.
These humans know Homo.
I call that Divine Sandstorm.